Finding Aid for the Moore, Norman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Moore, Norman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0303
.21 linear_feet
Scope and Content
This collection contains copies of letters from 3 Union Soldiers to Norman Moore, during the Civil War. The letters discuss the war, lives of the soldiers, lives of people in Tennessee and Mississippi, crime in Nashville, and the death of President Lincoln. Several letters are fragmented pieces, and 2 letters are severely faded.
- Correspondence — from Newton Chaffe
  - Scrapbook, 1940s
  - original faded, June 10, 1862
  - December 5, 1863
  - January 17, 1864
  - ½ of letter, March 6, 1864
  - April 6, 1864
  - August 29, 1864
  - January 5, 1865
  - January 28, 1865
  - March 27, 1865
  - ½ of letter, April 11, 1865
  - regarding the death of President Lincoln, April 23, 1865
- Correspondence — from Jerry Rogers
  - March 14, 1865
  - April 18, 1865
  - ½ of letter (2), n.d.
- Correspondence — from cousin
  - ½ of letter, n.d.
- Correspondence — from brother
  - December 1, 1863 - original badly faded